

CAREER OVERVIEW

A Successful and Focused Professional with more than 9 years of experience and A proven knowledge of educating students from Pre-Primary to Master's Degree in ICT-Computer Science and Technology, Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the desired position.

CORE SKILLS

- Exceptional Communication and Strong Interpersonal Skills.
- Asp .NET using Visual Studio (v. 2005 2022)
- Core Java using Net-Beans(v.7-12)
- Python (basic) using Pycharm 2020.
- MS-Office.
- Struts-2.0 and Hibernate-3.0.

CONTACT

Mail: panchalniraj.panchal@gmail.com Phone: (+91)8460761225

Address:

23, Manu Panchal Society, Bhimjipura, Nava Vadaj, Opp. Janak Medical Stores, Near Mojani Seva Sadan, Ahmedabad - 380013, Gujarat, India.

NIRAJ PANCHAL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Teacher Condigal Technologies 9th May 2022 - Present

 An experienced Coding Teacher teaching block based and web based coding in various programming languages on hourly basis.

ICT Teacher Shreyas Foundation 25th May 2021 - 30th April 2022

 An Experienced ICT - Computer Teacher in GSEB Secondary (English & Gujarati Medium) and Higher Secondary (English Medium Arts, Science & Commerce) on contract basis from 25 May 2021 to 30 April 2022.

ICT Teacher Kameshwar International School September 2020 - April 2021

• An Experienced ICT - Computer Teacher in CBSE
Higher Secondary Department teaching "Live"
Python Programming using Pycharm 2020-21
software, HTML,.NET through Zoom Meeting,
Google Meet, MS-Teams, Extra Marks and MS Skype Meeting & experience in maintaining
websites, software installation, uploadingdownloading and other back office related work.

ICT Teacher Swaminarayan Dham International School May 2019 - May 2020

- An Experienced ICT Computer Teacher in ICSE Pr-Primary and Primary and GSEB Pr-Primary to Higher Secondary.
- Experience in maintaining websites, software installation, uploading-downloading and other back office related work apart from teaching.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Department Of Computer Science, Kadi Sarva Vishwavidyalaya, Gandhinagar

- Master Of Science In Information Technology
- June 2010 June 2012

J.G. College Of Computer Applications, Gujarat University

- Bachelor Of Computer Applications
- June 2007 June 2010

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Reading Inspirational Books(You Can Win - Shiv Khera, Road To Success -Napolean Hill).
- Surfing Technological Websites.
- Listening Music & Singing

ICT Teacher Asia English School June 2017 - May 2019

- An Experienced ICT Computer Teacher in CBSE Secondary and GSEB Higher Secondary Department.
- Experience as an ICT Teacher in GSEB Govt.
 Grant-In-Aid Higher Secondary and CBSE
 Department.

ICT Teacher The H.B Kapadia New High School June 2016 - May 2017

- ICT Teacher in CBSE Pre-Primary to Secondary and GSEB Higher Secondary Department.
- Successfully completed CBSE Training and certification in 21st Century, Computer Science Curriculum by Next Education CBSE.

Software Developer - Asp.Net Tejasvi I.T Solutions June 2014 - June 2016

 Developed product Life Insurance Premium Calculation and Premium Reminder System on Asp.Net Framework - 4.0 as a Front End and Microsoft SQL Server - 2014 as a Back End using Microsoft Visual Studio - 2012 for L.I.C Agent.

Software Developer - Asp.Net Live Bird Technologies July 2013 - June 2014

• Software Developer on Asp .NET MVC using Framework-4.0 & MS SQL Server-2008 as a back-end using entity framework and entity data model using Microsoft Visual Studio 2012.

Assistant Professor-M.sc.I.T and M.B.A, K.S School Of Business Management, Gujarat University July 2012 - June 2013

• Assistant Professor in M.Sc.I.T and M.B.A Department, Gujarat University teaching subjects as per University requirement.

Profile Summary

- Experience in teaching Live Online Programming in Python, C, C++ through apps.
- Experience as Coding & ICT Computer Teacher.
- Educating Students from Pre-Primary to Master's Degree since 2012.